Political Research Associates Records MS014
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Subject files, 1949 -- 2010; MS014.003; 78.0 Cubic Feet
  - Comit Evangelico para Ayuda al Desarrollo (CEPAD) Nicaragua / Evangelical Council for Relief and Aid to Development, 1988 -- 1993; MS014.005661; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Committee for Correspondence anti-creationist, 1982; MS014.005662; 2 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Committee For a Free Afghanistan, 1983 -- 1990; MS014.005663; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Committee for a Pro-Family America, 1998; MS014.005664; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Freedom and Justice, 1982; MS014.005665; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee for Human Action Coalition, 1982; MS014.005666; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Open Debate on the Holocaust, 1995 -- 1996; MS014.005667; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 15)
    This folder contains Holocaust denial materials.
  - Committee for Positive Reform, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005668; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Committee for the Common Man, 1981; MS014.005669; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Committee on the Present Danger, 1976 -- 1990; MS014.005670; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Committee for the Free World, 1981 -- 1990; MS014.005671; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Committee for the Scientific of Claims of the Paranormal, circa 1994 -- 1997; MS014.005672; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Committee of the Survival of a Free Congress, 1982 -- 1983; MS014.005673; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Committee in Solidarity with People of El Salvador (CISPES), 1983 -- 1988; MS014.005674; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Committee of Ten Million, circa 1979; MS014.005675; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Committee for the States, 1987 -- 1991; MS014.005676; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Arrangements, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005677; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Committee to Avert a Mid-East Holocaust, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005678; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Contains only a cross reference sheet."
  - Committee to Defend Liberty Lobby, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.005679; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Committee to Impeach Bill Clinton, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005680; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Committee to Protect the Family Foundation, 1987 -- 1990; MS014.005681; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 29)
    This folder contains homophobic rhetoric relating to the AIDS epidemic.
  - Committee to Restore the Constitution, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005682; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Committees of Correspondence, circa 1990 -- 1994; MS014.005683; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Common Language Defense Fund, 2001; MS014.005684; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Common law court movement, 1996; MS014.005685; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Commonwealth Foundation for Public Policy Alternatives, 1996 -- 1997; MS014.005686; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Communication Institute, circa 1976 -- 2009; MS014.005687; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Communism / Anti, circa 1982 -- 1988; MS014.005688; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Communitarian, 2003; MS014.005689; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Community, The (YAHSHUA), circa 1984 -- 1997; MS014.005690; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 38)
    This folder contains a pamphlet with homophobic language.
  - Community Control Group of Lord's Order / Straight Community Order, 1987; MS014.005691; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 39)
    This folder contains an extortion attempt and threats of violence.
  - Computers - racists - bulletin board system (BBS) - Burghart, 1996; MS014.005692; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 40)
    This folder contains materials describing antisemitic, racist, and xenophobic web forums and activities.
  - Computers - racists online - articles, 1985 -- 2001; MS014.005693; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 41)
    This folder includes articles and news releases discussing online racist groups and terrorism.
  - Far-right electronic networks, 1985 -- 1996; MS014.005694; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Computers - racist - BBS, circa 1984 -- 1985; MS014.005695; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 43)
    This folder contains Ku Klux Klan newsletters that include racist and antisemitic rhetoric.
  - Computers - racist - text, 1985 - -1993; MS014.005696; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Concerned Women for America, circa 1982 -- 2000; MS014.005697; 2 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 45-46)
  - Concerned Women for America publications, circa 1991 -- 1992; MS014.005698; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Concerned Women for America (CWA) 1993 -- 1995 (direct mail), MS014.005699; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Concerned Women for America Massachusetts, 1994 -- 1998; MS014.005700; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Concerned Women for America, 1986 -- 1992; MS014.005701; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Concerned Women for America 2000 -, 1997 -- 2004; MS014.005702; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Concern for Dying, circa 1981 -- 2004; MS014.005703; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Concerned Citizens, circa 1981 -- 2004; MS014.005704; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Concerned Women for America, 1996 -- 2000; MS014.005705; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Concord Books, 1986; MS014.005706; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Conference of the States, 1995; MS014.005707; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Congregation for the Doctrine of the Faith, 1985; MS014.005708; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1989 -- 1991; MS014.005709; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Club, 1981; MS014.005710; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Human Rights Foundation, 1990 -- 1993; MS014.005711; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Majority Committee, 1886 -- 1987; MS014.005712; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Policy Institute, 1984; MS014.005713; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Quarterly, 1983; MS014.005714; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Connerly, Ward, 1999 July; MS014.005715; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Conservative Action Foundation, 1986; MS014.005716; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Conservative Alliance, 1984 -- 1990; MS014.005717; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Conservative Baptist Home Mission Society, 1987 October 05; MS014.005718; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Conservative Bookclub, circa 1981 -- 1998; MS014.005719; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Conservative Campaign Foundation, 1994 March 02 -- 1994 April 26; MS014.005720; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Conservative Catholics, 1986 -- 1997; MS014.005721; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Conservative Caucus, circa 1982 -- 1999; MS014.005722; 2 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 23-24)
  - Conservative Caucus / National Lawyers Guild, 1983 -- 2009; MS014.005723; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Conservative Caucus Research, Analysis and Education Foundation, 1983 -- 1994; MS014.005724; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Conservative Chronicle, 1992 -- 2003; MS014.005725; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Conservative Digest, 1985 -- 1989; MS014.005726; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Conservative Generation X, 1996 June 13 -- 1996 October 09; MS014.005727; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Conservative Jews, 1993 -- 1997; MS014.005728; 1 Folder(s) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference 7th annual, 1995; MS014.005729; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference, 1994 -- 1996; MS014.005730; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference 5th annual, 1993; MS014.005731; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference, 1992; MS014.005732; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference 3rd annual, 1991; MS014.005733; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference 2nd annual, 1990; MS014.005734; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Conservative Leadership Conference 1st annual, 1989; MS014.005735; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Conservative Leadership Political Action Committee (PAC), 2000; MS014.005736; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Conservative Network, 1989 -- 1995; MS014.005737; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - American Conservative Union (ACU) and Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 1977 -- 1978; MS014.005738; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Conservatives for a Winning Ticket, circa 1975 -- 2004; MS014.005739; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference, 1981 -- 1999; MS014.005740; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Conservative Research Center, 1994; MS014.005741; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Conservative Review, 1992 -- 1994; MS014.005742; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Conservative Television Network, 1993; MS014.005743; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Conservative Victory Committee, 1996; MS014.005744; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Conservative Victory Fund, 1982 -- 1994; MS014.005745; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Conservative Youth of America, 1997; MS014.005746; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Conservatives Against Liberal Legislation, circa 1975 -- 2004; MS014.005747; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Consortium for International Citizen Exchange, 1981; MS014.005748; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Conspiracy theories, 1979 -- 1994; MS014.005749; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Constitution Party of the state of Washington, circa 1975 -- 2004; MS014.005750; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1982 -- 1983; MS014.005751; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Constitutionalists, 1995; MS014.005752; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Consumer Alert, 1990 -- 1999; MS014.005753; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Container Supply Company, 1988; MS014.005754; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Contingency Preparation Consultants, 1990 February; MS014.005755; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Continuity, circa 1992; MS014.005756; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Contra Aid, circa 1984 -- 1988; MS014.005757; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Contra Aid Network lists, 1985 -- 1987; MS014.005758; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Contract on America, 1995; MS014.005759; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Cooperative Baptist Fellowship, 1991; MS014.005760; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Cooperative Housing Foundation / Fundacin Para la Vivienda Cooperative, 1982 -- 1993; MS014.005761; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Coors brewery, circa 1981 -- 1998; MS014.005762; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Coors brewery: annual reports, 1989 -- 1992; MS014.005763; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Coors - notes, circa 1989 -- 1990; MS014.005764; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Coors, 1975 -- 2004; MS014.005765
    - Coors family, 1975 -- 1990; MS014.005766; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Coors / Correspondence, 1994; MS014.005767; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Coors, Joseph, 1975 -- 1989; MS014.005768; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Coors Foundation, 1988 -- 1992; MS014.005769; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Coors Movement Against Racism and the Klan (MARK) lawsuit, circa 1981; MS014.005770; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Coral Ridge Ministries 2000 -, 1999 -- 2004; MS014.005771; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Coral Ridge Ministries, circa 1986 -- 2000; MS014.005772; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Corcoran, Tom, 1983 -- 1984; MS014.005773; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Corporate Air Service, 1986; MS014.005774; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Costa Rican Democratic Association, 1989; MS014.005775; 1 Folder(s) (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1968 -- 1978; MS014.005776; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Council for a Competitive Economy, circa 1982; MS014.005777; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Council for a Livable World Education Fund, 1996 September -- 1996 November; MS014.005778; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Council for the Defense of Freedom, 1982 -- 1990; MS014.005779; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Council for Democratic and Secular Humanism, circa 1994 -- 1995; MS014.005780; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Council for Inter-American Security, circa 1981 -- 1993; MS014.005781; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Council for Inter-American Security Santa Fe, 1980 -- 1989; MS014.005782; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Council for the National Interest, circa 1993; MS014.005783; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Council for National Policy II, MS014.005784
    - Council for National Policy (CNP) -- Lists of Members, 1984 -- 1985; MS014.005785; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Council for National Policy, circa 1985 -- 1996; MS014.005786; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - CNP -- National Conservative Policy Advisory Council -- 1983 List, 1983 -- 1990; MS014.005787; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Council for National Policy - Meetings, Annual, MS014.005788
    - CNP, 1993; MS014.005789; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - CNP, 1990; MS014.005790; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - CNP, 1988; MS014.005791; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - CNP, 1989; MS014.005792; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - CNP, 1985; MS014.005793; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - CNP, 1984; MS014.005794; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - CNP, 1982; MS014.005795; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Council for Volunteer Americans, circa 1990; MS014.005796; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Council of Conservative Citizens, 1990 -- 2001; MS014.005797; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Council of Volunteer Americans, circa 1995; MS014.005798; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Council of the Americans (Affiliate of Americas Society), 1980 -- 1993; MS014.005799; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1975 -- 1993; MS014.005800; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Council on Southern Africa, circa 1968 -- 2001; MS014.005801; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Counterinsurgency (Drugs), circa 1987 -- 1988; MS014.005802; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Couple to Couple, 1989 -- 1999; MS014.005803; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Court-stripping, circa 1982; MS014.005804; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Covenant House Association / Casa Alianza, circa 1987 -- 1991; MS014.005805; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 28)
    This folder contains clippings and news releases relating to religious pedophilia, child abuse, and murder.
  - Covenant, Sword, and Arm of the Lord, 1985; MS014.005806; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Covert Action, 1989; MS014.005807; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1988 February; MS014.005808; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Craig Shirley and Associates, 1999 February 12; MS014.005809; 1 Folder(s) (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Crane, Daniel, 1982 -- 1984; MS014.005810; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Crane, Philip M., 1981 -- 1984; MS014.005811; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Creation Moments, 1999; MS014.005812; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Creation Research Society, 1990 -- 1993; MS014.005813; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Creation Science Ministries, circa 1973 -- 2009; MS014.005814; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Creationism, 1981 -- 1999; MS014.005815; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Creative Associates International, 1990 -- 1991; MS014.005816; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice, 1983 -- 1987; MS014.005817; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Criminal Justice Legal Foundation, 2004 -- 2006; MS014.005818; 2 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Crisis, 1992 -- 2000; MS014.005819; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Danielle Crittenden, 1999; MS014.005820; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Catholic Relief Services (CRS) audits / Programs finance, 1980 -- 1982; MS014.005821; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Catholic Relief Services (CRS), circa 1979 -- 1983; MS014.005822; 3 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
  - CRS, 1981 -- 1983; MS014.005823; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - CRS - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1982; MS014.005824; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - CRS Clips - general news, 1973 -- 1983; MS014.005825; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - CRS finance, 1975 -- 1982; MS014.005826; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - CRS - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) requests, circa 1979; MS014.005827; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - CRS - Guatemala, 1982; MS014.005828; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Croatia - Ushashi, 1973 -- 1985; MS014.005829; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Crossway Books, 1989; MS014.005830; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Crosswinds, 1992 -- 1994; MS014.005831; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Crozier, Brian, 1984; MS014.005832; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Crucial Concepts, 1993; MS014.005833; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Cuba, 1983 -- 1991; MS014.005834; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Cuban Right, 1974 -- 1988; MS014.005835; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Cuban American National Foundation, circa 1985 -- 1994; MS014.005836; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Cuban Exiles, 1988; MS014.005837; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Cults, 1974 -- 1996; MS014.005838; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Cult Awareness Network (CAN), circa 1992 -- 1995; MS014.005839; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Culture of Life Foundation, 1998 August; MS014.005840; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Czechoslovak National Council of America, circa 1973 -- 2009; MS014.005841; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Dallas Theological Seminary, 1991; MS014.005842; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Mary Daly, 1996 -- 1999; MS014.005843; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - D'Amato, Alfonse M., circa 1983 -- 1989; MS014.005844; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Danforth, John C., 1982; MS014.005845; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Daniels, LeGree, 1982; MS014.005846; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - German American National Congress (DANK), 1987; MS014.005847; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Dannemeyer, Representative William, circa 1986 -- 1994; MS014.005848; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Dart Industries, 1984; MS014.005849; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Dartmouth College, 1995; MS014.005850; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Dartmouth Review, The, circa 1982 -- 2009; MS014.005851; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Data Center, The, 1984 -- 2005; MS014.005852; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Dave Bossie Investigative Report, 1999; MS014.005853; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Day, Lorraine, 1991; MS014.005854; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - DC Student Coalition Against Racism (DC SCAR), circa 1973 -- 2009; MS014.005855; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Death culture, 2001 -- 2002; MS014.005856; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Death penalty, 1991; MS014.005857; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Deaver, Michael K., 1986; MS014.005858; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Declaration Alliance, The, 2004; MS014.005859; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Declaration Foundation, circa 1973 -- 2009; MS014.005860; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Deceptive Fundraising and Organizing, 1990; MS014.005861; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - DeConcini, John D., 1989; MS014.005862; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Dector, Midge, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.005863; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Defenders of Life, 1993 -- 1997; MS014.005864; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Defenders of the Defenders of Life, 1994; MS014.005865; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Defensive action, 1994 -- 1995; MS014.005866; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Defense spending, circa 1989; MS014.005867; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Defending the left, 1981 -- 1995; MS014.005868; 1 Folder(s) (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Delgaudio, Eugene A., 1992; MS014.005869; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Delphi Research Associates / Delphi International Group, circa 1984 -- 1990; MS014.005870; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Delphi Schools, 1992; MS014.005871; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - DeMar, Gary, circa 1952 -- 2007; MS014.005872; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, circa 1994 -- 2007; MS014.005873; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Conservative Forum, 1980; MS014.005874; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Leadership Council (DLC), 1989 -- 1990; MS014.005875; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Dent, Harry S., 1981; MS014.005876; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Committee, circa 1952 -- 2007; MS014.005877; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - DeMoss Foundation, 1999; MS014.005878; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Denton Amendment, 1984 -- 1987; MS014.005879; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Denton, Jeremiah, circa 1981 -- 1986; MS014.005880; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Paul de Parrie, 1995; MS014.005881; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Derwinski, Edward, 1989 -- 1990; MS014.005882; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Desegregation, 1981 -- 1982; MS014.005883; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Desert Publications, circa 1952 -- 2007; MS014.005884; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Deukmajian, George, 1982 -- 1984; MS014.005885; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Devine, Donald J., 1982; MS014.005886; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - DeVos, Richard, 1981 -- 1986; MS014.005887; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Deweese Report, 2000; MS014.005888; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Dickson, Sam G., circa 1952 -- 2007; MS014.005889; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Dillon, C. Douglas, 1989; MS014.005890; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Dilys, Joseph, circa 1952 -- 1984; MS014.005891; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 23-25)
    These folders contain materials with holocaust denial, and include materials with racial slurs and racist, antisemitic rhetoric.
  - Direct Relief International, 1986 -- 1990; MS014.005892; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Disarmament, 1982 -- 1983; MS014.005893; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Discipleship Journal, circa 2004; MS014.005894; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Disinformation, circa 1982; MS014.005895; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Dispatches, circa 1990; MS014.005896; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Diversity Alliance for a Sustainable America, 2000 -- 2001; MS014.005897; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Dobson, Dr. James, 1970 -- 2003; MS014.005898; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Dolan, Terry, 1981 -- 1987; MS014.005899; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Dole, Bob, circa 1992; MS014.005900; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Elizabeth Dole, 1999 January -- 1999 June; MS014.005901; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Donahue, Thomas R., 1988 -- 1989; MS014.005902; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - The William H. Donner Foundation, Inc., 1991; MS014.005903; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - (Thomas A.) Dooley Foundation / Intermed USA, 1963 -- 1990; MS014.005904; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Donovan, Raymond, 1982; MS014.005905; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Dornan, Robert K., 1983 -- 1988; MS014.005906; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Douglass, Frederick, 1985 -- 1999; MS014.005907; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Dowling, Thomas, 1987; MS014.005908; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Downey, Morton, 1988; MS014.005909; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Draper, Reverend James T., Jr., 1982 -- 1982; MS014.005910; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Drudge, Matthew, 1999; MS014.005911; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Drug movement, anti-, 1988 -- 2003; MS014.005912; 1 Folder(s) (Box 21, Folder 46)